# Sasha Luka

# Software Engineer

Inspired back-end developer with broad experience in Javascript/ES6, React framework. 1.4 years experience with Python using Django.

## **PROJECTS**

# Sugar Snaps — Django Web App

Project for Columbia City Community. Social share application with Django, CSS, and Bootsrap4. Designer, Creator, Researcher, ScrumMaster. Features I implemented were the entire models. Resolved issues for following, signout, and css styles. Enjoyed designing and testing features. Other features are the following: user profile, user rating, forum, delete user and posts.

## **Twitter Clone** — React Web App

React web application, nodes, css, bootstrap. Scrum Master. Writing and testing code for efficiency. Allocating tasks from a scrum table and upkeep the progress. Implemented components state, how to fetch data from an external API and how to store and display it.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **UIE Coach** — Kenzie Academy

April 2020 - August 2020 // Indianapolis, Indiana

Helping students understand the concepts of react, redux, asynchronous, and api's. Test student submissions and follow up with feedback. Basic shell commands and troubleshooting version control issues. Best practices in clean code.

## Office Manager — Sweeney's Country Style Meats

January 2017 - March 2019 // Bremerton, WA

Clerical duties and operations. Training, delegating, and assisting associates after assigning daily tasks. Receiving, invoicing, pricing, inventory and loss prevention. Supervising sanitation and safety.

## Lead Mixologist — Stixx & Stones Billiards

July 2013 - August 2017 // Bremerton, WA

Food industry operations. Catering events. Designed promotions for local artists, comedians, and musicians. Building and maintaining relationships with customers, vendors, and producers. Sales of high end billiard cues and gear. Updating the menus and maintaining social media presence

## **Senior Product Specialist** — Ashley Furniture Homestore

June 2012 - September 2014 // Silverdale, WA

Create, design, and coordinate desirable room settings. Established customer relationships and followed up after orders to assure exceptional services. Showed flexibility to achieve sales and was noted for "zero order errors" on the company POS systems.



Seattle, WA 98118



github.com/slukas111



sashamati@gmail.com



(206) 458-5527

#### **SKILLS**

#### Front-end

Javascript, Html5, CSS, ReactJS, JSX, Bootstrap

#### Backend

Python, Django, PostSQL, Ninja

## **Tools**

Git, RestAPIs, VS code Editor, Github, Gitlab, Linux

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Kenzie Academy**

Full-Stack Developer Certificate

July 2019 - July 2020

12 month program for adults career transitioning with industry relevant skills. Develop problem-solving and technical skills.

## **Olympic College**

Computer Science AA

March 2013 - Pursuing

Photoshop, Art & design technical, rock climbing club.

#### **INTERESTS**

Calisthenics, CBT, beginner yoga, variety art medium, reading, repairing electronics

## **React Portfolio**